(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T23:13:07.879313",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
こんこよー！こよりだよー！
Konkoyo! It's Koyori!
せーの！ こんこよー！
Ready, set... Konkoyo!
はい！ ハッシュタグ #こより実験中 でしたー！
Yes! That was hashtag #KoyoriExperimenting!
OK!
こよは...
Koyo is...
頭脳です！
the brain!
頭脳ですか？
You're the brain?
はい、やったー！
Yes, yay!
頭脳でーす！
I'm the brain!
てれん！ はい！ せーの！
Ta-da! Yes! Ready, set!
研究所らしい実験！
A proper lab experiment!
うわー！ 20時実験！
Woah! 20:00 experiment!
こよりの朝食はネム！
Koyori's breakfast is Nem!
うわー！ ヘルプ！
Woah! Help!
うわー！ 助けてー！
Woah! Help me!
そうなんですね！ 見えたー！
Is that so? I see it!
可愛いー！ やー！
So cute! Yay!
OK! こんこよー！
OK! Konkoyo!
うわー！ やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Woah! Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a drink!
脳に刺激を！
Stimulate the brain!
はい！ お肉！ 実験！
Yes! Meat! Experiment!
冷凍うどんは常備してます！
I always stock frozen udon!
そうですか？ はい！
Is that so? Yes!
やったー！ 証明完了 Q.E.D.！
Yay! Proof completed, Q.E.D.!
コックだろコック
You're a cook, right? A cook!
こよりは、ちくわを作る
Koyori makes chikuwa!
大丈夫か？ ういーういーういーういー！
Are you okay? Wee wee wee wee!
うわー！ 行きませんね！
Woah! It won't go!
思い出しましょう！
Let's remember!
精神のプログラムをあげよう！
Let's raise the mind's program!
あー！ はい、もう！ こよりー！
Ah! Oh come on! Koyori!
うー！ やったー！
Ooh! Yay!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a drink!
脳に刺激を！
Stimulate the brain!
はい！ お肉！ 実験！
Yes! Meat! Experiment!
冷凍うどんは常備してます！
I always stock frozen udon!
そうですか？ はい！
Is that so? Yes!
私の戦闘力は54万です
My power level is 540,000.
しかも私は変身を残しています
And I still have transformations left.
雨の日のツインテール最高
Twintails on rainy days are the best!
たけのこの里が好き
I like Takenoko no Sato!
うわー！ 150、50！
Woah! 150, 50!
チャウチャウは乗り物ではありません
Chow chows are not vehicles.
コラーゲンです
It's collagen!
尻尾を振っちゃダメです
You shouldn't wag your tail!
みんなの応援が必須なんだよー！
Everyone's support is essential!
見ててー！
Watch me!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a drink!
脳に刺激を！
Stimulate the brain!
はい！ お肉！ 実験！
Yes! Meat! Experiment!
冷凍うどんは常備してます！
I always stock frozen udon!
そうですか？ はい！
Is that so? Yes!
やったー！ せーの！
Yay! Ready, set...
こんこよー！
Konkoyo!
こよりだよー！
It's Koyori!
せーの！ こんこよー！
Ready, set... Konkoyo!
はい！ ハッシュタグ #こより実験中 でしたー！
Yes! That was hashtag #KoyoriExperimenting!
OK!
こよは...
Koyo is...
頭脳です！
the brain!
頭脳ですか？
You're the brain?
はい、やったー！
Yes, yay!
頭脳でーす！
I'm the brain!
てれん！ はい！
Ta-da! Yes!
せーの！
Ready, set!
研究所らしい実験！
A proper lab experiment!
うわー！ 20時実験！
Woah! 20:00 experiment!
こよりの朝食はネム！
Koyori's breakfast is Nem!
うわー！ ヘルプ！
Woah! Help!
うわー！ 助けてー！
Woah! Help me!
そうなんですね！ 見えたー！
Is that so? I see it!
可愛いー！ やー！
So cute! Yay!
OK! こんこよー！
OK! Konkoyo!
うわー！ やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Woah! Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a drink!
脳に刺激を！
Stimulate the brain!
はい！ お肉！ 実験！
Yes! Meat! Experiment!
冷凍うどんは常備してます！
I always stock frozen udon!
そうですか？ はい！
Is that so? Yes!
やったー！ 証明完了 Q.E.D.！
Yay! Proof completed, Q.E.D.!
コックだろコック
You're a cook, right? A cook!
こよりは、ちくわを作る
Koyori makes chikuwa!
大丈夫か？ ういーういーういーういー！
Are you okay? Wee wee wee wee!
うわー！ 行きませんね！
Woah! It won't go!
思い出しましょう！
Let's remember!
精神のプログラムをあげよう！
Let's raise the mind's program!
あー！ はい、もう！ こよりー！
Ah! Oh come on! Koyori!
うー！ やったー！
Ooh! Yay!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a drink!
脳に刺激を！
Stimulate the brain!
こよはマヨネーズで回復した
Koyo recovered with Mayonnaise.
助手くんが仲間になった！
Assistant-kun joined the party!
AIこよりが仲間になった！
AI Koyori joined the party!
もふこよが仲間になった！
Mofukoyo joined the party!
ヘイ!
Hey!
カロスを照らすあの朝日のように
Like that morning sun lighting up Kalos,
(ニトロチャージ熱くいこうぜ)
(Nitro Charge, let's go with heat)
さあ! 進もうぜ いつでも準備は OK
Come on! Let's move forward, always ready, OK!
(型破り変幻自在で)
(With a mold-breaking, shape-shifting style)
重なり合う想いがシンクロして
Our overlapping feelings synchronize,
決して消えない絆になるから
and become an unbreakable bond.
どこまでも強くなれる
So we can grow stronger without end,
俺たちなら Woh woh woh yeah
if it's us! Woh woh woh yeah!
行くぜ! 激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go! An intensely burning battle!
行くぜ! ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go! A pinch is a chance!
いこうぜ! 起死回生
Let's go! Reversal from the brink of death!
絶対に諦めない
We will never give up!
俺たちは諦めない
ヘイ! たとえどんな壁が道を塞いだって
Hey! Even if any wall blocks the path,
(いつでも当たって砕けろで)
(always crashing through it)
さあ! この手で勝利の星を掴むんだ
Come on! With these hands let's grasp the star of victory,
(折れない不屈の心で)
(with an unbroken, indomitable heart)!
俺たちはいつでもどんな時も
We are always, at any time,
同じ心で繋がってるから
connected with the same heart,
何度でも立ち上がるぜ
so we will stand up again and again!
お前となら
If it's with you!
行くぜ! 手強いライバルたち
Let's go! Formidable rivals!
行くぜ! 決めろ一撃必殺!
Let's go! Land a one-hit sure-kill!
いこうぜ! 負けられない思いがここにあるから
Let's go! Because the feelings of not wanting to lose are right here!
夢が俺にはあるから yeah
Because I have a dream, yeah!
博衣こより生誕ライブ2026見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to watch Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026!
神ゲーたちの神ゲームソングをいっぱい詰め込んでるので、最後まで楽しんでいってね！
I've packed full of legendary game songs from legendary games, so please enjoy until the very end!
行くぜ! 勝ちも負ける痛みも
Let's go! Both victory and the pain of defeat,
行くぜ! 何でも分け合える
Let's go! We can share everything!
いこうぜ! 仲間がいる
Let's go! We have our companions!
俺たちは一人じゃない!
We are not alone!
行くぜ! 激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go! An intensely burning battle!
行くぜ! ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go! A pinch is a chance!
いこうぜ! 起死回生
Let's go! Reversal from the brink of death!
絶対に諦めない
We will never give up!
行くぜ! 譲れない夢がある
Let's go! We have a dream we cannot yield!
行くぜ! 必ずGETだぜ
Let's go! We'll definitely get it!
いこうぜ! 手を伸ばして
Let's go! Reaching out our hands,
いつか描いた未来へ
towards the future we once pictured,
誰も知らん高みへ yeah
to the unknown heights, yeah!
さあ! 上げてくぜ (100万ボルト)
Come on! Let's power up (100,000 Volts)!
そう! 立ち向かって共に行こうぜ
That's right! Let's face forward and go together!
見たことのない夢の向こうまで
Beyond the unseen dreams!
はーい！みんな、こんばんはー！
Hi! Good evening, everyone!
ホロライブ6期生秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm the brain of Hololive 6th generation Secret Society holoX, Hakui Koyori!
改めて、今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Once again, thank you so much for coming to Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026 today!
コメントもいっぱいありがとう！イエーイ！こよ見えてるよ！ありがとう！
Thank you for all the comments too! Yay! Koyo can see you! Thank you!
ということで、ライブの感想やスクショは #博衣こより生誕ライブ2026 をつけてたくさんポストしてください！
So, please post lots of your live reactions and screenshots with #博衣こより生誕ライブ2026!
目指せ トレンド入り！ よろしくね！
Let's aim to get trending! Thanks for your support!
はい！ということで 息が整ってないですけど...
All right! So, I'm still a bit out of breath, but...
さて、今年の生誕ライブ、テーマは『ゲームソングLive』です！
Now then, the theme for this year's Birthday Live is "Game Song Live"!
これまでたくさんやってきた実況配信で
From all the game streams I've done so far,
一緒に遊んできた思い出のゲームや
I've packed in songs from memorable games we played together
こよりが大好きなゲーム関連の楽曲をたくさん詰め込みました！
and games that I absolutely love!
最後まで全力で楽しんでいってね！
Please enjoy it to the fullest until the very end!
ということで1曲目は大好きなポケモンの「XY&Z」を歌わせていただきました！ね！
So, for the first song, I sang "XY&Z" from Pokémon, which I love! Right!
助手くん！「オレはこいつと旅に出る」っていうことです！
Joshu-kun! It means "I'm going on a journey with this guy!"
はい、Xでセトリ予想もね、みんなにたくさんしてもらっていたんですけど、
Yes, everyone was posting lots of setlist predictions on X,
ポケモンの予想は結構多かったですけど、「XY&Z」当てられてる人は結構少なかったです！
and while there were many Pokémon guesses, very few people guessed "XY&Z"!
当たった君、おめでとう！
To those who got it right, congratulations!
ま、この曲はZ-Aが発表されたっていうのもあるんですけど、
Well, partly because Z-A was announced,
歌詞がめっちゃ良くて、実はこよりにもピッタリな曲なので選びました！
but the lyrics are so great, and it fits me perfectly, so I picked it!
さぁ、この後も自分の予想が当たってるかな〜ってドキドキしながら楽しんでいってください！
Now then, please continue to enjoy while being excited to see if your predictions come true!
新3D衣装お披露目もあるからね！絶対に最後まで見ていってね！
There's also the new 3D outfit reveal, so make sure to watch until the very end!
それでは、そろそろ次の曲。
Now then, it's about time for the next song.
ゲームの世界へ... どうぞ！
Into the world of games... Here you go!
気がついたら 同じ面ばかりプレイ
Whenever I realize it, I'm playing the same stage over and over,
そしていつも 同じ場所で死ぬ
and I always die at the exact same spot.
あきらめずに 消える足場に挑戦するけど
Without giving up, I keep trying the disappearing footholds,
すぐに下に落ちるよ
but I immediately fall to the bottom!
アイテム2号があれば 楽に向こうの岸までつくけど
If I had Item No. 2, I could easily reach the other side, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Air Man!
あの竜巻 何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge those tornadoes.
後ろに回って 撃ち続けても いずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I get behind him and keep shooting, eventually the wind blows me away!
タイム連打も ためしてみたけど
I tried rapid-pausing the game, too,
竜巻相手じゃ 意味がない！
but against tornadoes, it's completely useless!
だから次は絶対勝つために
So to make sure I win next time,
僕はE缶だけは 最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Tank until the very end!
気がついたら ライフもう少ししかない
Before I know it, I barely have any life left,
そしていつも そこでE缶使う
and so I end up using my E-Tank right there.
あきらめずに エアーマンまでたどり着くけれど
Without giving up, I manage to reach Air Man,
すぐに残機なくなる
but I quickly lose all my remaining lives...
リーフシールドがあれば 楽にエアーマンを倒せるけど
If I had the Leaf Shield, I could easily defeat Air Man, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
ウッドマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Wood Man!
落ちる木の葉は 何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge those falling leaves.
後ろに下がって 距離をとっても いずれは距離を詰められる
Even if I step back and keep my distance, he eventually closes the gap!
タイム連打も ためしてみたけど
I tried rapid-pausing the game, too,
あいつのジャンプは くぐれない！
but I can't slide under his jumps!
だから次は絶対勝つために
So to make sure I win next time,
僕はE缶だけは 最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Tank until the very end!
アイテム2号があれば 楽に向こうの岸までつくけど
If I had Item No. 2, I could easily reach the other side, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Air Man!
あの竜巻 何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge those tornadoes...
何回やっても避けれない
No matter how many times I try, I can't avoid it.
後ろに回って打ち続けても
Even if I get behind him and keep shooting...
いずれは風に飛ばされる
...I eventually get blown away by the wind.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I tried the time barrage too, but...
竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
...against the tornado, it's useless!
だから次は絶対勝つために
So next time, to win for sure...
僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
...I'll save my E-Tank until the very end!
倒せないよ
I can't defeat him!
あてもなく 彷徨っていた
Wandering aimlessly without a purpose,
手がかりもなく 探しつづけた
I kept searching without a single clue.
あなたがくれた 思い出を
The memories you gave to me,
心を癒す 歌にして
I turn into a song that heals the heart.
約束もすることもなく
Without making any promises,
交わす言葉も決めたりもせず
without deciding on words to exchange,
抱きしめ そして確かめた
we held each other close and made sure
日々は二度と帰らぬ
that those days will never return.
記憶の中の
In my memories,
手を振るあなたは
as you wave your hand—
わたしの名を呼ぶことが出来るの
can you still call out my name?
あふれる その涙を
Turn those overflowing tears
輝く勇気に変えて
into shining courage.
いのちは続く
Life goes on,
夜を越え
beyond the night.
疑うことのない
Unwavering,
明日へと続く
leading into tomorrow.
飛ぶ鳥の向こうの空へ
Into the sky beyond the flying birds,
いくつの記憶預けただろう
how many memories have I left behind?
はかない希望も夢も
Fleeting hopes and dreams,
届かぬ場所に忘れて
forgotten in a place out of reach.
めぐり逢うのは
Is meeting each other
偶然と言えるの
truly just a coincidence,
別れる
even though a time to part
ときが必ず来るのに
will inevitably arrive?
消えゆく 運命でも
Even if fate fades away,
きみが生きている限り
as long as you are alive,
いのちは続く
life goes on.
永遠に その力のかぎり
Forever, with all its strength,
どこまでも
wherever it may lead.
わたしが
Even after
死のあとも
I am gone,
きみが生きている限り
as long as you are alive,
いのちは続く
life goes on.
永遠に その力のかぎり
Forever, with all its strength,
どこまでも続く
continuing on forever.
わたしは何色ですか
What color am I to you?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう 陽の光を
I shall give you the light of the sun.
悲しみが溢れ
As sadness overflowed,
瞼閉じました
I closed my eyes.
こぼれた滴は
The overflowing drops
心に沁みゆく
soak into my heart.
行き渡る波は
The waves that spread
弱く交えます
weakly intertwine.
届けしゆりかご
The delivered cradle
眠りをさそう
invites sleep.
夢になつかしい
In a dream, I search
面影を探す
for a nostalgic trace of you.
手を伸ばし
Reaching out my hand,
強く抱きしめたくなる
I begin to want to hold you tight.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I to you?
藍深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep indigo,
渡そう高き空を
I shall give you the high sky.
不安定な神様
An unstable god,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
a cycle of encounters and farewells.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we meet again,
時かける旅人
a traveler leaping through time.
あなたが泣いている
You are crying,
流るる涙の雨
a rain of flowing tears.
泣くなとは言わない
I won't tell you not to cry
心かなしくて
when your heart is so sad.
生きとし生けるもの
All living things
何かを背負いながら
carry a burden as they live,
見えない鎖に
bound together
つながれている
by invisible chains.
どれほど救われただろう
I wonder how much I've been saved.
あどけない笑顔を
Your innocent smile,
なくしたくはない
I never want to lose it.
不安定な神様
An unstable god,
繰り返す過去と未来
a cycle of past and future,
生まれそして死んでゆく運命
a destiny of being born and dying.
掛け違えた世界で
In a mismatched world,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
a cycle of encounters and farewells.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we meet again,
時かける旅人
a traveler leaping through time.
けがれのない心
A pure, unblemished heart,
黒く染めゆきながら
even as it is stained in black,
抑えられなくて
unable to be suppressed,
解き放たれる
it is set free.
何回名前を呼んだだろう
How many times have I called your name?
あどけない笑顔は
That innocent smile
もうどこにもない
is nowhere to be found anymore.
不安定な神様
An unstable god,
引き継いだ夢と愛を
...inheriting dreams and love,
育て守り託しゆく運命
the destiny to nurture, protect, and entrust them.
掛け違えた世界で 探すたび引き裂かれても
In a mismatched world, even if we are torn apart searching,
また会えると信じて 時かける旅人
believing we will meet again, travelers crossing time.
不安定な神様 繰り返す過去と未来
Unstable god, repeating past and future,
生まれそして死んでゆく運命
the destiny of being born and then dying.
掛け違えた世界で 繰り返す出会いと別れ
In a mismatched world, repeating meetings and partings,
また会えるその日まで 時かける旅人
until the day we can meet again, travelers crossing time,
until the day we can meet again, travelers crossing time.
はい！ということで、Suaraさんにお越しいただき、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
Alright, so Suara-san came to join us, and we sang together!
Suaraさん、自己紹介をいただいてもよろしいでしょうか？
Suara-san, would you mind introducing yourself?
はい！Suaraです。『うたわれるもの』シリーズの主題歌をたくさん歌っている者です！
Hi! I'm Suara. I've sung many theme songs for the Utawarerumono series!
はーい！ようこそー！
Yay! Welcome!
こよりさーん！
Koyori-san!
そうなんです！実はですね、『うたわれるもの』というゲーム、昨年約3ヶ月間かけてシリーズの三部作を実況プレイさせていただいたんですけれどもの、
That's right! Actually, last year I did a Let's Play playthrough of the Utawarerumono trilogy over about three months,
その『うたわれるもの』、本当に曲がめちゃくちゃいいのですが、その歌をほぼすべてSuaraさんが歌っていらっしゃるという！
and while the music in Utawarerumono is incredibly good, almost all of those songs are sung by Suara-san!
のです！
Exactly!
もう、耳が今日本当に幸せで！
My ears are just so happy today!
いや、こちらこそですよ、本当に！
No, the pleasure is all mine, really!
もう恐縮な恐れ多い状態なんですけれども、ありがとうございます！
I feel so humbled and honored, but thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
Suaraさんには実は4周年の時に逆凸でメッセージも頂戴しておりまして、
Actually, Suara-san gave me a message during my reverse call stream for my anniversary,
その時に「いつか一緒に歌いたい」というのも、こよりも結構熱烈なラブコールをさせていただいていたんですけれども、
and back then, I passionately sent my love call saying, "I want to sing with you someday!"
その思いを本日叶えることができました！
And today, that dream came true!
え、あの、ちょっと質問が何個かあるんですけれども、
Um, well, I have a few questions for you...
実話『うたわれるもの』の実況をしていた時に、最終回でSuaraさんがコメントをしてくださいまして、
When I was streaming Utawarerumono, Suara-san actually left a comment on the final stream,
はい！
Yes!
こよりの実況をちょっとご覧くださったと思うんですけれども、見られますか？実況とかって普段…
I think you watched a bit of my stream, but do you usually watch Let's Plays?
ちょっと実はですね、初めて見させていただいて…
To be honest, that was actually my first time watching one...
そうなんですか！？
Really?!
あの、アクアプラスのスタッフの方からも、「こよりさんが『うたわれ』配信してるよ」って、
The staff at Aquaplus told me, "Koyori-san is streaming Utawarerumono!"
情報は聞いていたんですよ。で、私のライブに来てくれるファンの方たちからも、
I had heard about it. And fans who came to my live shows also...
聞いてたんですよ。「ぜひ見てみてください」って言われて。それで見させていただいたのが…
told me about it, saying, "Please check it out!" So I ended up watching...
あの最終回だったんですけれども…
...that final episode...
そうだったんですね！恐縮です！
So that was it! I'm so honored!
本当にこよりさんの『うたわれるもの』への愛がすごい溢れてて、本当に見てて最後までずっと…
Your love for Utawarerumono was just overflowing, and watching you, I stayed until the very end...
うわー！
Wow!
見させていただいて。
...and watched it all.
で、「コメント送りたいな。あ、でももう早くしないと終わっちゃう！」って思いながら、
I was thinking, "I want to send a comment. Oh, but if I don't hurry, it'll end!"
で、同じ部屋に私の息子がいたんですけれども…
And my son happened to be in the same room...
あ、はい！息子さんまで！
Ah, yes! Even your son!
息子に「コメントちょっと送ってみていいと思う？」って言ったら、
I asked my son, "Do you think it's okay if I send a comment?"
「いいんじゃない？」って言われて…
and he said, "Why not?"
いい息子さんだ！
What a great son!
それで本当に震える手でコメントを打って、もう「早くエンターキーを…」
So with trembling hands, I typed out the comment, thinking, "Hurry and press Enter..."
そんな緊張してくださってたんですか！？
You were that nervous?!
「遅いか遅いか？あーどうしよう！でも早く押さな！」みたいに思いながら…
Thinking, "Is it too late? Oh, what should I do? But I have to press it fast!"
はい、それで、もうドキドキしながら、
Yes. So, nervous and heart pounding,
あの、送らせていただいたら、
um, after I sent it,
皆さんね、あの、コメント気づいてくださって。
everyone noticed my comment.
はい！もう！
Yes! Really!
とっても嬉しかったです！こよりもですし、見てた助手さんたちも、
I was so happy! Both me and the assistants watching,
ものすごくもう嬉しくって。やっぱり、あの、見ていただけるっていうのが、
were so ridiculously happy. Having you watch us,
Suaraさんとか、あの、アクアプラスさんもそうですし、
like Suara-san and AQUAPLUS as well,
その公式の皆さんにご覧いただけるって本当に嬉しく恐縮なことなので、
to have the official staff watch us is truly such a humbling and happy thing,
もう幸せでございました。ありがとうございます！
I was so happy. Thank you so much!
もうすごい楽しくて見入っちゃいました、本当に。
It was so fun, I was completely glued to it, really!
すごい長時間配信されているのがすごいなと思って、本当に。
I thought it was amazing that you streamed for such a long time, really.
その日の夜も歌枠も聞かせていただいたり。
And that night I listened to your singing stream too.
すごい体力だなーと思いながら。
I was thinking, "What incredible stamina!"
楽しんでるのもね、『うたわれるもの』が本当に素晴らしい作品だったから。
You enjoyed it so much because "Utawarerumono" is such a wonderful work.
ですので、その『うたわれるもの』とずっと付き合っていらっしゃる、
So, Suara-san, who has been involved with "Utawarerumono" for so long,
Suaraさんなんですけれども、
I wanted to ask...
推しキャラとかっていらっしゃるんですか？
do you have a favorite character?
推しキャラですか？推しキャラはやっぱりちょっとエルルゥっていうことに...
A favorite character? Well, I have to go with Eruruu...
エルルゥっていうことにしておかないとね、
If I don't say Eruruu,
ちょっとフォークで刺されるかもしれない。
I might get stabbed with a fork.
あ！あれ？もしや...中の人が仲が良い...
Ah! Wait, could it be... you mean the person inside is close with...
中の方の柚木涼香さんとね、とっても仲良くさせていただいてて。
The voice actor, Ryoka Yuzuki-san, I'm very close friends with her.
本当にアニメの放送の時からですね、
Really, ever since the anime broadcast,
2006年からずっと仲良くさせて...
from 2006, we've been close friends...
20年！
20 years!
そうですね。20年。
That's right. 20 years.
はい。もうそれはエルルゥ推し...ですね！
Yes. So I have to be an Eruruu fan... indeed!
ということもあって、エルルゥ推しということで、お願いします。
So for that reason, please sign me down as an Eruruu fan.
こよりはアルルゥが大好きなので、エルルゥ・アルルゥで、
Koyori loves Aruruu, so between Eruruu and Aruruu,
姉妹で！
they're sisters!
嬉しいです！
I'm so happy!
はい、ということで、もっとお話ししたいんですけれどもの、お時間が来てしまいまして！
Yes, so we want to talk so much more, but time has already run out!
本当に今日は一緒に歌っていただきありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for singing with me today!
こよりさんの本当に柔らかい、優しい、温かい、
Surrounded by Koyori-san's really soft, gentle, and warm...
声に包まれながら、私も一緒に歌えて本当に幸せでした。
...voice, I was truly happy to be able to sing together with you.
恐縮でございます！ありがとうございます。
I'm so honored! Thank you so much.
また是非色々ご一緒させていただける機会があれば嬉しいです！
If there's another opportunity to work together again, I'd be so happy!
是非是非！よろしくお願いします。ありがとうございます！
By all means! I look forward to it. Thank you so much!
と、いうことで、Suaraさんでしたー！
And with that, that was Suara-san!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
こよりのリズムラボ
[Koyori's Rhythm Lab]
9th リミックス
[9th Remix]
やがて女はきれいになるだろう
[Song: It Won't Be Long Before Women Get Pretty]
だいスキ！
I love you!
人に媚びての人生
Living a life pleasing others,
本当の自分に出会えない
you can't encounter your true self.
あのダンスがsexy 君はいい女なんだ
That dance is sexy, you're a fine woman.
あのキスしてcrazy 君はまんまで素敵だよ
Kissing like crazy, you're wonderful as you are.
輝きたい 愛されたい
I want to shine, I want to be loved.
歴史がほおっておかない
History won't leave you alone.
華やか人生生きたい
I want to live a glamorous life.
ah 悲しい歌流れる
Ah, a sad song plays...
街の中歩く
as I walk through the town.
涙が流れちゃう
Tears keep falling down,
tears keep falling down,
涙が流れちゃうのは どうしてなんだろう
I wonder why tears keep falling down.
ワン ツー スリー で ワン ツー スリー きれいになる
One, two, three, one, two, three, becoming beautiful!
だから恋破れて 誰も信じられなきゃ
So if you're heartbroken and can't trust anyone,
泣きたいだけ泣けばいい
just cry as much as you want.
ワン ツー スリー で ワン ツー スリー きれいになる
One, two, three, one, two, three, becoming beautiful!
だからまた恋して 時に夢中すぎて
So fall in love again, and even if you get too absorbed...
まわりが見えなくなってもいいじゃない
...and lose sight of your surroundings, that's okay!
だいスキ！
I love you!
こっち見て！
Look over here!
マジだいスキ！ だいスキ！
I really love you! I love you!
愛♡スクリーム！
[Song: Ai Screamin!]
教えて！もっと あなたのこと
Teach me more about you!
Tell me more, more, more, more!
聞かせて！もっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice!
Let me hear more, more, more!
こんなドキドキ もう抑えきれない
This excitement, I can't hold it back anymore
Oh! All I need you!
Oh! All I need is you!
友達は卒業 運命の私 見つけてほしいの
Moving past being friends, I want destiny to find me
One! 勇気を出して
One! Summon up the courage
Two! 見つめる作戦
Two! Strategy of gazing
Three! 瞳と目が合えば Fall...
Three! When our eyes meet, I fall...
止められない
Can't stop this!
Yeah, yeah, yeah この恋 この愛で Melt, melty 溶けちゃうよ
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this romance and love, I'm melting away
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
届け！大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
Okay!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
こよりちゃん！
Koyori-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
マヨネーズよりも あなた！
More than mayonnaise, I like you!
あずきちゃん！
AZKi-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
こしあん つぶあん よりも あなた！
More than smooth or chunky bean paste, I like you!
らみちゃん！
Lamy-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
お酒よりも あなた！
More than alcohol, I like you!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き こよみー！
Of course, we love Koyo-me!
止められない
Can't stop this!
Yeah, yeah, yeah この恋 この愛で Melt, melty 溶けちゃうよ
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this romance and love, I'm melting away
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
届け！大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
Okay!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
お願い 見つけて my darling
Please find me, my darling
お願い 気づいて my darling
Please notice me, my darling
One! 勇気を出して
One! Summon up the courage
Two! 近づく作戦
Two! Strategy to get closer
Three! 手と手が触れて Fall...
Three! When our hands touch, I fall...
止められない
Can't stop this!
Yeah, yeah, yeah この恋 この愛で Melt, melty 溶けちゃうよ
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this romance and love, I'm melting away
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
それは！あなた！
That person is you!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
Okay!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
Okay!
愛 Scream 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's scream it out loud!
Scream! アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
La-la-la-la-la love, love...
もう何十回？
How many dozens of times?
もう何百回？
How many hundreds of times?
かすむ空見上げて
Looking up at the hazy sky,
たどり着いた場所が
the place I've reached is...
因縁のダイヤモンド
the fateful diamond.
何千回？
How many thousands of times?
何万回？
How many tens of thousands of times?
涙流した君へ
To you who shed tears...
ねえ 諦められた言葉はあったっけ？
Hey, were there words that could be given up?
憧れは限界かな？
Is longing at its limit?
もういらない 評価にただ黙るなんて
I don't need to stay silent about unwanted evaluations anymore,
勿体ないでしょ？
wouldn't that be a waste?
それぞれの物語
Each of our stories,
交差する瞬間を
the moments where they intersect,
見つめる日々は
these days watching them...
放ちたい夢だけ
Only the dreams we want to unleash,
大きな声抱いて
holding onto loud voices,
弾けそうな煌めきも
even the radiance that seems about to burst,
消えることなく
without ever fading away,
どこまででも
no matter how far,
世界の向こうに
to the other side of the world,
届くよ
it will reach!
終わることのない
Never ending,
この胸の衝動は
this urge inside my heart,
どうして？ どうして？ 守るフリをして
Why? Why do you pretend to protect,
痛むから
because it hurts?
その先へと
Heading beyond that,
走り続ける
continuing to run,
次へ 次へ
on to the next, to the next!
妄想だった 中途半端な
It was a delusion, half-baked,
深さ抱えて 立ち尽くしていた
carrying depth, I was standing frozen,
理屈通り
as logic dictates,
雨はプレリュード
the rain is a prelude.
何千回？
How many thousands of times?
何万回？
How many tens of thousands of times?
挑み続けた君へ
To you who kept challenging...
ねぇ 聞かせてよ 夢は叶うんだって
Hey, tell me that dreams do come true!
諦めが簡単ならば
If giving up were easy,
絶対にならないようで
it seems it would never happen,
誰に邪魔させようと
no matter who tries to interfere,
躊躇わないで
don't hesitate!
重なった情熱を
The accumulated passion,
音はずさず繋いでいく
connecting without missing a beat,
そう 最後まで
yes, until the very end!
暗闇に近い
Close to darkness,
星く閃いて
shining like stars,
鳴り止まないファンファーレ
an unceasing fanfare,
いつもの心に
in the usual heart,
流れていた
that was flowing,
遠い未来へ
towards the distant future,
祈るよ
I pray.
忘れられない
Unforgettable,
あの日の後悔も
even the regrets of that day,
追いかけて 追いかけて 滑り込んだ この想い
chasing, chasing, sliding into this feeling,
青い空に
into the blue sky,
溢れてた
overflowing,
遠く 遠く
far, far away!
目覚めては繰り返す 眠い朝は
Awakening again and again, on sleepy mornings,
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tightly fasten the tie on my collar.
教室のドアくぐると ほんの少し
Stepping through the classroom door, just a little bit,
胸を張って歩き出せる
I can puff out my chest and walk forward.
そんな日常に 吹き抜ける風
A breeze blowing through such everyday life,
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it,
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I felt it,
震え出す 今この胸で
beginning to tremble now in this chest,
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was coming already,
幾億の星が消え
billions of stars disappear,
去っていくのを
and depart...
見送った
I watched them go.
手を振った
I waved,
よかったね、と
saying, "I'm glad."
廊下の隅見下ろす 掃除の途中
Overlooking the corner of the hall while sweeping,
おかしなものだと思う
I think something is odd.
あたしの中の時は止まってるのに
Even though time within me has stopped,
違う日々を生きているように
it's like I'm living different days.
埃は雪のように降り積む
Dust falls and piles up like snow.
待ってる気がした
I felt like I was waiting.
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like someone was calling out.
震え出す今この時が
Now this moment begins to tremble,
見つけた気がした 失われた記憶が
I felt like I found it, lost memories
呼び覚ました
awakened.
物語
A story
永遠の
of eternity,
その終わり
and its end.
いつの間にか駆け出してた
Before I knew it, I was running,
あなたに手を引かれてた
led by your hand.
昨日は遠く 明日はすぐ
Yesterday is far away, tomorrow is right ahead,
そんな当たり前に心が躍った
my heart raced at such simple things.
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it,
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I could feel it.
震え出す今この胸で
Now trembling in my heart,
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was coming already.
幾千の朝を越え 新しい陽が
Crossing thousands of mornings, a new light
待ってる気がした
I felt like it was waiting,
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like it was calling out.
震えてるこの魂が
This trembling soul
見つけた気がした
felt like it had found it.
幾億の夢のように消え去れる日を
The day that vanishes like hundreds of millions of dreams...
見送った
I watched it fade,
手を振った
I waved,
ありがとう、と
saying, "Thank you."
ぽつり 灯り 管制塔
A lonely light, the control tower,
砂嵐の向こうへ
toward the other side of the sandstorm,
祈るように 綴った
written like a prayer,
これからのこと
about what lies ahead.
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous Requested.
お便り 届いてますか
Has my letter reached you?
この世界が いつからか
Since when did this world
まるで 他人事のように
feel like someone else's business?
やけに 静かなので
Because it's so terribly quiet,
不安になったのです
I became anxious,
思い出したのです
and I remembered.
人知れず 口をつぐんだまま
Keeping my mouth shut without anyone knowing,
終われないのです
I cannot let it end,
それは 嫌なのです
I hate that.
夢ってもっと わがままだったでしょう
Dreams were supposed to be more selfish, right?
応えてよ 笑ってよ 気付いてよ
Answer me, laugh, notice me!
此処に居るのにな 意地悪だな
Even though I'm right here... you're being mean.
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one...
どうしたら 伝えられるのでしょう
How can I convey it to you?
どうしても 伝えたいよ
No matter what, I want to tell you!
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio Name: Requesting Anonymity
意地悪 意気地なしなのでしょうか
Is it mean-spirited, or am I just a coward?
それともこの世界には 僕はお邪魔でしょうか
Or in this world, am I just an intrusion?
だとしても綴るよ
Even so, I'll write it down.
みっともなく透けるよ
Translucent and unseemly,
振られたって好きだよ いいでしょ
Even if rejected, I love you... Isn't that okay?
いいでしょ
Isn't that okay?
楽しかったよね
It was fun, wasn't it?
悔しかったよね
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
もう独り言は嫌だ
I'm tired of talking to myself.
「待たせちゃったかな」
"Did I keep you waiting?"
「別に待ってないよ」
"I wasn't really waiting."
夢と呼んだそれも僕だっただけ
Even what we called a dream was just me.
もういいかい もういいよ
"Are you ready?" "I'm ready."
応えてよ 笑ってよ 気付いてよ
Answer me, smile for me, notice me!
此処に居るのにな 意地悪だな
Even though I'm right here... You're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one,
ぼくだけは 光と呼び続ける
Only I will keep calling it light.
真夜中 管制塔から
From the control tower in the dead of night,
世界を明かしてやる
I will illuminate the world for you.
特報
[Special Announcement]
応えてよ 笑ってよ 気付いてよ
Answer me, smile for me, notice me!
此処に居るのにな 意地悪だな
Even though I'm right here... You're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one...
どうして変えれないのでしょう
Why can't it be changed?
どうしても伝えたいよ
I want to convey it no matter what.
ライブ終了直後 プレミア公開
[Premiering right after the live stream]
ということで！
And with that!
新曲のお披露目、フルアニメーションMV公開の告知、
Unveiling the new song, announcing the full animation MV release,
新3Dのお披露目！3個どどん！とまとめてやらさせていただきました！
and revealing the new 3D model! I presented all three at once!
イエーイ！
Yay!
情報量多かったですけど、追いついてるかなー？
There was a lot of information, but are you all keeping up?
はい！ちょっとね新3Dが可愛すぎて気になっちゃうと思うんですけど、
Alright! I know the new 3D model is so cute that you're distracted by it,
まずはオリ曲の話からさせてください！
but first, let me talk about the original song!
お披露目させていただいたのは新曲「管制塔より」！
The new song I unveiled was "Kanseitou Yori"!
ついにあの掘江晶太さんに書き下ろしていただきました！
Horie Shota-san written and composed this brand new song for me!
みんな、どうだったー？
Everyone, how was it?
エモい？よかったー？
Was it emotional? Did you like it?
はい！そしてですね、今ちょっと映像も流して「すごい」って言ってくれててめっちゃ嬉しいんですけど、
Yes! And right now, as the clip plays, seeing everyone say "amazing" makes me so happy,
このライブ終了直後にフルアニメーションMVがプレミア公開されます！
but right after this live stream ends, the full animation MV will premiere!
たぶんもうあの、マネちゃんがポチってしてくれてると思います！
I think my manager has already clicked the button to set it up!
世界観がめちゃくちゃこだわり抜かれている映像作品になっているので、
The worldview of this video project has been crafted with so much care,
何回も見たり聞いたり、あと世界観の考察とかしてみてくだーさい！
so please watch it, listen to it, and analyze the worldview over and over!
そして！お待たせしました！
And now, thank you for waiting!
あ、ちょっと待って！1個言い忘れました！
Ah, wait! I forgot to mention one thing!
さっきの曲「管制塔より」、24時に音源リリースもあります！よろしくお願いします！
The song "Kanseitou Yori" will also be released digitally at midnight! Please check it out!
そしてですね、お待たせしました！新3Dー！
And now, thank you for waiting! The new 3D model!
どう？可愛い？可愛い？可愛いー？！
How is it? Cute? Cute? Super cute, right?!
はい！もっとね、余すことなく見せたいんだけど、
Yes! I want to show it off without holding anything back,
ちょっとももこママのあれ、いつものにすごい近くなったんじゃないかなーと思います！
but I think it turned out super close to Momoko-mama's original design!
この後のメン限ライブでね、撮影会もしまして、
In the members-only stream after this, we'll have a photo shoot session,
さらに細かく見せちゃうので、ぜひメン限ライブも来てください！
and I'll show off even more details, so please come join the members-only stream too!
メン限ライブでは本編で歌えなかったあのゲームの、みんなが大好きな曲、
In the members-only stream, I'll sing that super popular game song everyone loves,
KinKinKinKinも歌うよ！お楽しみに！
KinKinKinKin, which I couldn't sing in the main stream! Look forward to it!
じゃあ、1つだけ新3Dのめっちゃ変わったポイント教えちゃうと…
Alright, let me tell you one super big change in this new 3D model...
けもの耳が揺れます！
The animal ears twitch and wiggle!
うわー！可愛いー！
Woah! So cute!
えー、あ、あとトレンド1位も本当にありがとうございます！
Ah, and thank you so much for getting us to #1 on trending!
今日厳しいかなって思ってたから トレンド1位めっちゃ嬉しかったし
I thought it'd be tough today, so I was super happy about #1 on trending,
トレンド爆散 なんかすごいっぱい入ってたみたいで 本当にありがとー！
and seeing so many related terms flood the trending list! Thank you so much!
それでは！もうひとつ、大事なお知らせでーす！ドーン！
Now then, here's another very important announcement! Ta-da!
博衣こより 誕生記念グッズ2026が 発売されまーす！
Hakui Koyori Birthday Celebration Goods 2026 are now on sale!
イエーイ！早速詳細を見ていきましょう！
Yay! Let's check out the details right away!
まずひとつ目はこちら！「もふこよにもなる！？2Wayブランケット」！
First up is this! "Becomes Mofukoyo too?! 2-Way Blanket"!
お部屋でゲームを楽しんでいる こよりの描き下ろしイラストです！
It features a new illustration of Koyori enjoying games in her room!
イラストはもちろん ももこママ！
Illustrated, of course, by momoco-mama!
これ丸めると もふこよに早変わりして 持ち運びも楽ちんだし そのまま飾っても可愛いですね！
Roll it up, and it turns into Mofukoyo! It's super portable, and it looks adorable displayed as is!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ボイスキーホルダー 〜ゲーム実況編〜！
"Voice Keychain ~Game Commentary Edition~"!
待望のボイスキーホルダーが出ました！こよりの撮り下ろしボイスが入っているもので
The long-awaited voice keychain is here! It comes with freshly recorded voices from Koyori,
今回はライブに合わせて ゲーム実況中っぽいセリフ、絶叫が 6種類入っております！
and to match this stream's theme, it features 6 types of game commentary lines and screams!
セリフはこよりが考えました！
I came up with all the lines myself!
イラストは なもり先生です！
Illustrated by Namori-sensei!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
こより監督ぬいぐるみスマホスタンド！
"Director Koyori Plushie Smartphone Stand"!
あのこより監督がついにぬいぐるみになったよー！
Director Koyori has finally been turned into a plushie!
可愛ーい！
It's so cute!
そのまま飾るもよし、スマホスタンドにもなるので超便利です！絶対ゲットしてね！
Great for display, plus it functions as a phone stand, so it's super handy! Be sure to get one!
最後はこちら！
And finally, this!
ゲーム機風カードホルダー！
"Game Console-Style Card Holder"!
特典のチェキ風ブロマイドとかトレカも入れられて、持ち運べちゃうカードホルダーです！
You can slip in the bonus check-style bromide or photo cards and carry them around!
中に入っている台紙のイラストは こよちゃんが描き下ろした！
The illustration on the insert card inside was drawn by me, Koyo-chan!
ゲーム機風のデザインもレトロゲームっぽくて可愛くない？
Doesn't the retro game console design look super cute too?
はい！そしてフルセット特典はこちらです！
Yes! And here are the full set purchase bonuses!
ももこママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドがつきます！
It comes with a check-style bromide illustrated by momoco-mama!
数量限定版は直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージ入り、通常版は箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りになってます！
The limited edition includes a hand-written signature and foil-stamped message, while the regular version includes a foil-stamped signature and message!
販売開始が、このあと21時...
Sales will start right after this at 21:0...
10分にしてあるので、皆さんあのあわてないで！
10! So everyone, please don't panic!
大丈夫です、10分からなので！
It's totally fine, sales start at 21:10!
はい！あの、見てってくだーい！よろしくお願いします！
So please stick around and check it out! Thank you!
さらに！特典ASMRボイスもつきます！
Plus! It also comes with bonus ASMR audio!
恒例の「君の誕生日を逆に祝っちゃうASMRボイス 2026版」！
It's the annual "ASMR Voice 2026: Celebrating YOUR Birthday Instead"!
こちらですね、毎年みんなが誕生日まで我慢して聞いて「わーい！」ってなってるの、すごく嬉しく思ってます！
Every year, hearing how everyone waits until their own birthday to listen and get super excited makes me so happy!
ぜひゲットしてください！
Please be sure to get it!
はい！ということで、怒涛のお知らせでしたが...
Alright! That was a whirlwind of announcements, but...
可愛いでしょー？みんなが可愛いって言ってくれてて、こよ嬉しいよ！
Isn't it adorable? Everyone's saying how cute it is, and Koyo is so happy!
表情とかもちょっと変わったんですよ！「にゃ〜！」
My expressions changed a little bit too! Look, "Nya~!"
これができるようになりました！あとは「キリッ」「イエーイ！」
I can do this now! Also, "Serious look" and "Yay!"
こんな表情もできるようになりました！メン限もお楽しみに！
I can pull off expressions like this now too! Look forward to the members-only stream!
ということで今日は、博衣こより生誕Live 2026「ゲームソングLive」に来てくれて、ありがとー！
So today, thank you so much for coming to the Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026 "Game Song Live"!
このあとですね、新曲のアニメMV公開と、メン限ライブ... あれですね！
After this stream, we have the premiere of my new song's animated MV, and the members-only live... wait!
アニメMV公開にて！で、10分からグッズ買って...
Right after the MV release, sales for goods open at 21:10...
15分からメン限ライブって感じで！
and then the members-only live starts at 21:15!
ゆっくり順番にいけるようになっているので、
Everything is timed so you can enjoy them one by one without rushing!
焦らず駆けず... なんだ、押さず？（笑）
No need to panic or scramble... wait, what was it, no pushing? (laughs)
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thanks, everyone!
ということで、今日はちょっと遅れちゃったんだけど、この3Dお披露目して、生誕ライブも来て、大好きなゲームソングいっぱいお披露目できて嬉しかったよ！
Even though we started a bit late today, I'm so glad I got to reveal this new 3D model, host my birthday live, and sing lots of my favorite video game songs!
みんな本当に見に来てくれて、ありがとー！
Thank you all so, so much for coming to watch!
また会おうね！ありがとー！
See you all again soon! Thank you!
MV見てねー！
Be sure to watch the MV!